President
总统
"Catch outside the ring"
“抓到圈外”
Damn. unbelievable
该死。难以置信
Mr. Bai.
白先生。
Give me the address of the woman who runs the café.
请给我经营咖啡馆的女士的地址。
These two idiots are ready to fight.
这两个白痴已经做好了战斗的准备。
You scoundrels.
你们这些无赖。
You bastards!
你这个混蛋！
the curse
诅咒
Come closer, you idiot!
靠近点，你这个白痴！
Screw you, you bastards! ‬
操你妈的，你们这些混蛋！‬
Damn
该死
You bastard
你这个混蛋
- They attacked him at the same time! - You scoundrel.
- 他们同时攻击他！ - 你这个恶棍。
the curse
诅咒
You fools!
你们这些傻瓜！
Come closer!
靠近点！
Scoundrel!
恶棍！
damn you
该死的你
Beat him up!
揍他一顿！
You trifle!
你这个小事！
You scoundrel!
你这个无赖！
the curse
诅咒
- You bastard! - You scoundrel!
- 你这个混蛋！ - 你这个恶棍！
Damn
该死
You idiot...
你个傻冒...
Come closer!
靠近点！
Screw it!
算了！
stand up! Move
起来！移动
- Let's leave, Gun-woo. - Okay.
- 我们走吧，建宇 - 好的
- Let's go!
- 我们走吧！
Thanks for coming, Hyun Joo.
谢谢你的到来，贤珠。
I apologize for coming late.
我为迟到而道歉。
You saved us from a severe beating.
你救了我们免遭毒打。
How painful. the curse
多么痛苦啊。诅咒
Is that you, Gun Woo?
是你吗，建宇？
"Gunwoo"?
“刚宇”？
Shut up.
住口。
- Move quickly. - Yes, sir.
- 快点行动 - 是的，先生
Hey you
嘿，你
Who is this
这是谁
How annoying.
真烦人。
the curse
诅咒
Wait.
等待。
Damn
该死
Who are you
你是谁
Shut your mouth, you bastard.
闭上你的嘴，你这个混蛋。
stand up
起来
Oh God, stop!
天啊，停下来！
What a view.
多么美妙的风景。
Hey you
嘿，你
who are you
你是谁
- Sorry, sir. - Stop.
- 对不起，先生 - 停下来
I asked you a question.
我曾问你一个问题。
sleep well
睡得好
What? What is this
什么？这是什么
When did you get this beating?
你什么时候受到这样的殴打？
Dear mom
亲爱的妈妈
Yes, mom.
好的，妈妈。
“Gun-woo.”
“枪宇。”
My mom? What happened? Why are you crying?
我的妈妈？发生了什么？你哭什么？
Someone wants to talk to you.
有人想和你说话。
where are you
你在哪
“Gun-woo.”
“枪宇。”
What happened to your forehead, mom?
妈妈，你的额头怎么了？
I'm fine
我很好
My head hit the ground.
我的头撞到了地上。
your face
你的脸
What happened to your face, Woo Jin?
宇进，你的脸怎么了？
It's just a scratch.
这只是一个划痕。
Mr. Choi felt very anxious while waiting for you.
崔先生 在等你的时候感到非常焦急。
Let's go down.
我们下去吧。
Well
好吧 _
I'll come back
我会回来的
Sit down, everyone!
大家坐下！
I'm sure you're very tired so I'll keep it short.
我确信你很累 所以我就长话短说吧。
When I received your call,
当我接到你的电话时，
I was shocked as if the world had ended.
我震惊了，仿佛世界末日来临了。
you are my family
你是我的家人
I was so afraid of losing you.
我是如此害怕失去你。
I will no longer tolerate you getting hurt.
我不会再容忍你受到伤害。
Let the adults handle the rest.
剩下的事情就让大人来处理吧。
-I want to help too. -Gun-woo.
-我也想帮忙。 -Gun-woo。
This is not a game that ends with a win or a loss.
这不是一场以胜利或失败结束的游戏。
This is a war that will not end until someone dies.
这是一场不有人死去就不会结束的战争。
Go upstairs.
上楼去。
- I'm sorry. - Promise me not to get yourself involved again.
-对不起 -答应我不要再卷入其中
Good
好的
They know where Gun Woo lives , so it's dangerous to go there.
他们知道建宇住在哪里 ，所以去那里很危险。
Take Gun Woo's mother to the orphanage tomorrow.
明天带建宇妈妈去孤儿院。
It would be safer for her to stay there.
对她来说，留在那里比较安全。
Good
好的
good night
晚安
What do we do now, Yang Jung?
杨正，我们现在该怎么办？
I'll put an end to it.
我会结束它。
We should have taken care of this a long time ago.
我们早就应该处理这个问题了。
Can you bring Myung-gil?
你能带明吉来吗？
I'll be forming a team with Do Young starting tomorrow.
从明天开始我将和道英组队。
- I'll target them one by one. - Let's eat with Do Young.
- 我会一一瞄准他们 - 我们和道英一起吃饭吧
Mr. Oh.
哦先生。
Investigate Myeong-gil's men, please.
请调查明吉的手下。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
I see you there since early morning , Mr. Director.
我从一大早就在那里见到你 ，主任先生。
I had to come for you, Mr. Kim.
我必须来找你，金先生。
I operated on them myself.
我自己给他们做了手术。
Good. I thank you
好的。我谢谢你
One of them had the Achilles tendons in both feet cut with a knife.
其中一人双脚跟腱被 刀割断。
The tendons in my other shoulder were torn.
我另一侧肩膀的肌腱撕裂了。
His hair is short
他的头发很短
His eyes are narrow.
他的眼睛很窄。
He was fast moving.
他动作很快。
His knife skills are excellent.
他的刀功非常出色。
Yes, actually...
是的，实际上...
It looked more like a sashimi knife.
它看起来更像一把生鱼片刀。
Damn
该死
Ask Beom to go to the office at one o'clock.
请Beom 一点钟去办公室。
- Let's meet. - Yes, sir.
- 我们见面吧 - 是的，先生
What is happening has become interesting.
正在发生的事情变得有趣了。
- Finish this. - Okay.
- 完成这个 - 好的
my lord
我的主
Yes
是的
I will accompany you.
我会陪你。
Stay here.
待在这。
I want to help sir.
我想帮助先生。
“Min Dong.”
“敏东。”
I'll take care of it myself.
我自己会处理的。
Live your life
过你的生活
I want to join you sir!
我想加入你，先生！
Listen
听
If the restaurant is destroyed by my return,
如果我回来后餐厅被毁了
So what will you do?
那么你会怎么做？
Protect the store. You can help me with this.
保护商店。你可以帮我解决这个问题。
But
但
Guard the store.
看守商店。
“Yang Jung Huang!”
“杨正晃！”
It's been a while.
有一阵子了。
Why haven't you been contacting me?
你怎么还不联系我？
I was busy making a living.
我正忙着谋生。
Why does your handsome face show signs of aging?
为什么你英俊的脸庞却显露出 衰老的痕迹？
Earning a halal livelihood is difficult.
赚取清真生计很困难。
is not it
是不是
It's very difficult.
这非常困难。
- It's been a long time. - Yes.
- 已经很久了 - 是的
I called Soo Cheol and Min Soo to ask them to investigate.
我打电话给秀哲和敏秀 ，请他们调查。
It's very complicated.
这非常复杂。
They are not ordinary moneylenders, there is something fishy about them.
他们不是普通的放债人， 他们身上有一些可疑之处。
Thanks
谢谢
A friend of mine heard in "Youido"
我的一个朋友在《Youido》中听到
The Il Group purchased an unfinished hotel building in Gangnam.
Il集团 在江南购买了一座未完工的酒店大楼。
They got their money from a company called Smile Capital.
他们的资金来自一家名为“微笑资本”的公司。
It's Myung Gil Kim's company.
这是金明吉的公司。
Okay
好的
But why would a chaebol borrow money from Myung Gil Kim? I don't understand it.
但为什么财阀会 向金明吉借钱呢？我不明白。
Most likely, Myung-Gil Kim tricked them.
最有可能的是，金明吉欺骗了他们。
- Let's investigate. - Okay.
- 我们来调查一下 - 好的
We will finally avenge our men.
我们最终将为我们的人报仇。
Let's end this issue.
让我们结束这个问题吧。
Mr. Choi gave us his approval.
崔先生给予了我们认可。
Good
好的
In the past, Chairman Choi had five appellants working for him.
过去，崔主席有 五名上诉人为他工作。
At that time, President Choi had loaned money to companies,
当时崔总统 向企业借钱，
He now has 10 billion won or more in uncollected money.
他现在有100亿韩元或更多 的未收回资金。
But places like real estate companies had gangs
但像房地产公司这样的地方却有黑帮
To guard her.
为了守护她。
And at times like this, these guys come out.
在这种时候，这些人就会出来。
They go out to eliminate an entire gang in a day.
他们出去一天之内消灭整个团伙。
At that time, even the major gangs were trembling in fear of stabbing Chairman Choi.
当时就连各大帮派都 颤抖着，生怕刺伤崔会长。
After I removed President Choi,
当我罢免崔总统后
The first thing I did with “Byom”
我对“Byom”做的第一件事
He is getting rid of his attackers.
他正在摆脱攻击者。
Do you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
No sir.
不，先生。
Because I was trembling in fear of them too.
因为我也因为害怕他们而颤抖。
Were you alone?
你一个人吗？
We sent two gangs, one from Sindang-dong and the other from Yeongdeungpo, and they were united.
我们派了两个帮派，一个来自新堂洞 ，一个来自永登浦，他们团结起来。
It only came about because they weren't together at the time.
只是 因为当时他们没有在一起。
Otherwise, it would be impossible to achieve this.
否则的话，就不可能实现这一目标。
Wow, how wonderful, sir.
哇，太棒了，先生。
But in the end,
不过最终，
I couldn't get rid of the two most important ones.
我无法摆脱两个最重要的。
Do Young Lee and Yang Jung Hwang.
李道英和黄杨正。
They are President Choi's right hand.
他们是崔总统的得力助手。
I met Do Young Lee once when I was Chairman Choi's servant.
当我还是崔主席的仆人时，我见过李道英一次。
he is handsome
他很帅气
One time, there was a gang leader who was stuck in a traffic jam.
有一次， 有一个帮派头目遇到了交通堵塞。
He smoked a cigarette with the car window open.
他打开车窗抽烟。
When he heard the sound of a motorcycle approaching, he turned his head.
听到摩托车驶近的声音， 他转过头。
Then Do Young Lee slit his face like this with a sashimi knife and walked away.
然后李道英 用生鱼片刀就这样割开了他的脸，然后走开了。
His mouth grew so large and began to tremble like this.
他的嘴巴张得那么大 ，并且开始像这样颤抖。
Damn, crazy.
该死的，疯了。
-And who is Yang Jung Hwang? -It is actually said...
-杨正黄是谁？ -实际上据说...
He incapacitated 20 gangsters
他使20名歹徒丧失行动能力
By tearing the Achilles tendons.
通过撕裂跟腱。
He fights with two knives,
他用两把刀战斗，
It is rumored that he stabs 100 times a minute.
据传他每分钟刺伤100次。
It's amazing and wondrous.
这是令人惊奇和奇妙的。
correct. Did you say those three guys showed up?
正确的。你说那三个人出现了？
Yes sir. A young woman appeared after some time passed.
是的先生。过了一段时间，一名年轻女子出现了。
I think it has something to do with the bookstore I told you about before.
我想这和我之前跟你说的那家书店有关系。
It makes sense that he would own a bookstore.
他拥有一家书店是有道理的。
Surely that damned senile old man crawled out of the darkness to save his children.
那个该死的老头子肯定 是从黑暗中爬出来拯救他的孩子们的。
Do you know how much President Choi owns?
你知道崔总统拥有多少财产吗？
Nearly 50 billion won in cash I think.
我认为现金接近500亿韩元。
This will save us money for the club.
这将为我们 俱乐部节省资金。
Surely there is a force in heaven looking after us, don't you think?
天堂里肯定有一股力量在照顾我们， 你不觉得吗？
Jang Do and Beom monitored the place and brought me everything there.
Jang Do 和 Beom 监视着这个地方，并把那里的所有东西都给我带来了。
"Loving Orphanage"
《爱心孤儿院》
Will not you come
你不来吗
I don't want to enter. Hurry up!
我不想进去。赶快！
Good. We'll be right back.
好的。我们马上回来。
- From here, children. - Look at this.
- 从这里开始，孩子们 - 看看这个
Please come from here.
请从这里过来。
It is a children's room so it is a bit small.
这是一个儿童房，所以有点小。
But it is suitable for residence, so take your time to inspect it.
不过适合居住， 有时间可以去考察一下。
Thanks
谢谢
What do you think about this place, mom? Look, it's Woo Jin.
妈妈，你觉得这个地方怎么样？ 看，这是宇进。
Hello ma'am
你好女士
A friend of mine from middle school
我的一个中学时代的朋友
He works for one of Myung-gil Kim's men, so he was on the scene that day.
他为金明吉的一名手下工作， 所以那天他就在现场。
What I heard was that the situation had reached a terrifying level.
我听到的是，情况 已经到了可怕的程度。
They were waiting for him at the gas station.
他们在加油站等他。
As soon as the Ile heir entered,
伊勒继承人一进来，
They imprisoned him, beat him, and threatened him.
他们监禁他、殴打他、威胁他。
They must be the only ones in Korea who would do this to a chaebol.
他们肯定是韩国唯一 会对财阀做出这种事的人。
and what else
还有什么
They have a video of the man...
他们有该男子的视频...
This is Jun Min Kim, Sales Director at Smile Capital.
我是 Jun Min Kim， Smile Capital 销售总监。
He has six records of fraud.
他有六项欺诈记录。
Scams related to used cars and credit cards, and he did not leave any type of them without practicing them.
诈骗涉及二手车和 信用卡，他不会在没有实践过的情况下留下任何类型的诈骗。
He apparently served his detention in the Seoul Nambu detention center.
他显然是在首尔南部拘留中心服刑的。
Jang Do Im was a student at the Police College.
张度任是警察学院的学生。
Until he was fired due to sexual harassment.
直到他因性骚扰而被解雇。
He has no previous records and is the head of strategic planning at Smile Capital.
他没有任何记录，是微笑资本的战略规划主管。
It's unusual.
这很不寻常。
The presence of a person familiar with how the police work
有熟悉警察工作方式的人在场
It will help them avoid police investigations.
这将帮助他们避免警方的调查。
Are these two people important?
这两个人重要吗？
Yes
是的
What about their address?
他们的地址呢？
I came up with this guy's address.
我想出了这个人的地址。
He lives in Saesong-dong.
他住在新城洞。
We know his car and its plate number.
我们知道他的车和车牌号。
We must act quickly.
我们必须迅速采取行动。
They will realize what is happening soon.
他们很快就会意识到发生了什么。
Okay
好的
I'll take care of this guy.
我会照顾这个家伙。
- Tomorrow night? - But what limit do we have in dealing with them?
- 明天晚上？ - 但我们对付他们有什么限制呢？
what do you mean? We must eliminate them once and for all.
你是什​​么意思？我们必须一劳永逸地消除它们。
I'll take care of Myung Gil Kim.
我会照顾金明吉的。
He does not move alone.
他并不是独自行动。
What he appears to be different from what he is. Go with Do Young.
他的外表和他的本质不一样。 和道英一起吧。
I'll just track him down.
我只会追踪他。
Wasn't there a burly person with Myung-gil?
明吉身边不是有一个魁梧的人吗？
Okay
好的
The detective agency asked for more time.
侦探社要求更多时间。
I will investigate further.
我会进一步调查。
who is he
他是谁
He's the man who threw me out the window and he's strong as a bull.
他就是那个把我扔出窗外的人 ，他像头公牛一样强壮。
Sir, what are you going to do with the money in the bookstore?
先生，你打算用书店里的钱做什么呢？
We must move it.
我们必须移动它。
He knows the place.
他知道这个地方。
Why don't we ask young people to move money?
为什么我们不要求年轻人转移资金呢？
The problem is that we do not have time and we lack manpower.
问题是我们没有时间 ，也缺乏人力。
They are strong.
他们很坚强。
- They got rid of 30 men. - Did you see what happened?
- 他们除掉了 30 个人 - 你看到发生了什么了吗？
I went there but they were lying on the ground.
我去了那里，但它们躺在地上。
The three of them were surrounded by 30 men and without knives...
他们三人被三十个人围住 ，而且没有带刀……
They are not ordinary guys.
他们不是普通人。
They won't have a problem if they move the money early in the morning, sir.
先生，如果他们一早就把钱转移的话，就不会有问题。
Why not give them a chance?
为什么不给他们机会呢？
Hyun Joo is smart too.
贤珠也很聪明。
Okay, let's put it here.
好吧，我们把它放在这里吧。
Please.
请。
It looks delicious.
看起来很好吃。
thank you
谢谢
- Thank you. - Pardon, hurry up and eat.
- 谢谢 - 对不起，快点吃饭吧
You first, Hyun Joo.
第一个是你，贤珠。
Fine, thank you
好的，谢谢
Did you use kimchi to prepare it?
你用泡菜来准备吗？
Yes
是的
It tastes completely different from the one I was making.
味道和我做的完全不一样。
The method is easy. I will teach it to you.
方法很简单。我会教给你。
Good
好的
I wanted to inquire about something.
我想询问一些事情。
Is Mr. Choi running the orphanage?
孤儿院是崔先生经营的吗？
Yes
是的
My grandfather was poor, according to his words.
用祖父的话说，他很穷。
His dream was to help those in need if he had abundant money.
他的梦想是如果他有足够的钱去帮助那些有需要的人 。
Good
好的
Are you his granddaughter then?
那你是他的孙女吗？
no. I was transferred to the orphanage after my parents died.
不。父母去世后，我被转移到孤儿院。
Good. I'm sorry
好的。对不起
Oh God. I shouldn't have brought this up.
天啊。我不应该提出这件事。
Never mind.
没关系。
I'm sorry
对不起
What food do you like, Hyun Joo?
贤珠你喜欢吃什么？
In reality
事实上
I love rolled omelettes.
我喜欢煎蛋卷。
Good. Eat some of these.
好的。吃一些这些。
Wow! Where is the rolled omelette?
哇！煎蛋卷在哪里？
You both had to leave some for Hyun Joo.
你们俩都得给贤珠留一些。
This is correct. I wanted her.
这是对的。我想要她。
Let me prepare more for you.
让我为你准备更多。
It's not your fault
这不是你的错
No, it won't take long. Wait a minute.
不，不会花很长时间。等一下。
Make it big and thick, mom.
妈妈，让它又大又厚。
Good
好的
Prepare a lot please.
请多多准备。
Okay, I'll make it big.
好的，我会把事情搞大的。
Hurry up and eat.
赶紧吃饭吧。
“Go to the bookstore the day after tomorrow and transfer all the money.”
“后天去书店，把钱都转过来。”
"(Jun Min Kim)"
“（金俊民）”
take care of yourself
照顾好你自己
- Have you packed everything? - Yes.
- 你把所有东西都收拾好了吗？ - 是的。
the curse. it's scary
诅咒。太可怕了
Start making boxes. I'll bring the money.
开始制作盒子。我会把钱带来。
How are we going to get her to the car?
我们怎样才能把她送上车呢？
We will carry it.
我们会携带它。
No, this will take too long. Vehicle security?
不行，这会花太长时间。 车辆安全？
Yes. It's in the storage room at the bottom left.
是的。就在 左下角的储藏室里。
Woo Jin and I will go get her.
我和宇进去接她。
Arrange the money on the floor.
把钱放在地板上。
- Okay. - Come on.
- 好的 - 来吧
How strong you are.
你有多坚强。
What do you do
你做什么工作
Don't let him catch you.
别让他抓住你。
- Who is he? - The man I told you about then.
- 他是谁？ - 就是我当时告诉你的那个人。
the curse
诅咒
Hit and dodge more quickly.
攻击和躲避速度更快。
Good
好的
You bastard.
你这个混蛋。
Damn
该死
damn it
该死的
just chill. Stop, that's enough.
冷静一下。停下来，够了。
its enough
够了
just chill
冷静一下
it's all over
一切都结束了
All is well
一切都很好
- Let's tie him up. - Yes.
- 我们把他绑起来 - 是的
- Let's find something to tie him to. - Okay.
- 我们找个东西把他绑起来吧 - 好吧
- Go check that side.
- 去检查那边 - 好的
the curse
诅咒
"Woo Jin!"
“宇进！”
critical
批判的
Wait.
等待。
What is this? What happened to you?
这是什么？你怎么了？
I had a fight.
我打了一架。
are you OK
你还好吗
I'm going to be in terrible pain tomorrow.
明天我会非常痛苦。
Why did you handcuff him in front? It will break it easily.
你为什么把他铐在前面？它会很容易打破它。
I do not think so
我不这么认为
Do they need to be tied up again?
还需要再绑起来吗？
Tie him up quickly. Bring the cart, Gun-woo.
赶紧把他绑起来。把车拿来，建宇。
Good
好的
Hold his feet.
握住他的脚。
Good. Let's go
好的。我们走吧
- Our jackets. - Damn. quickly
-我们的夹克 -该死 迅速地
These are expensive.
这些都很贵。
I handcuffed him here.
我把他铐在这里。
He escaped because you tied him to a pipe.
他之所以逃脱是因为你把他绑在管子上。
You had to get good at restraining him.
你得善于克制他。
Damn
该死
"(Jang Do Im)"
“（张道林）”
What delayed you?
是什么耽误了你？
We hit a snag.
我们遇到了障碍。
And wealth?
还有财富？
Don't worry. The money is still there.
不用担心。钱还在。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I can't reach InBome.
我无法联系 InBome。
My face and mouth were badly cut,
我的脸和嘴被严重割伤
So I'll go through the emergency
所以我会经历紧急情况
Before I return to the site of the event.
在我返回活动现场之前。
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
Clean up your mess before you leave.
离开前收拾好你的烂摊子。
Okay. You are right sir.
好的。先生，你是对的。
But my face is bleeding badly.
但我的脸流血得很厉害。
My teeth are loose, so I have to...
我的牙齿松动了，所以我必须...
You damned bastard.
你这个该死的混蛋。
Call Jung, gather his men and eliminate them immediately.
呼叫荣格， 召集他的手下并立即消灭他们。
I want their heads, okay? I see you trying to hold back, you bastard.
我想要他们的头，好吗？ 我看到你试图阻止，你这个混蛋。
Screw you. Do you want to die?
去你的。你想死吗？
Should I cut off your head before I cut off their heads, you idiot?
我应该在砍掉他们的头 之前先砍掉你的头吗，你这个白痴？
I will do what you ask.
我会按照你的要求去做。
Sir
先生
Move!
移动！
Get in the car quickly.
赶紧上车。
Arma!
阿玛！
- Open the trunk. - Okay.
- 打开后备箱 - 好的
Push it!
推它！
I notice
我注意到
quickly
迅速地
Damn
该死
Okay, we're done.
好的，我们完成了。
the curse. We have to get what's in the safe.
诅咒。我们得把保险箱里的东西拿出来。
Shouldn't we leave now?
我们现在不应该离开吗？
You are ahead of us.
你比我们领先。
How many are there?
那里有多少？
Billions at least.
至少数十亿。
I will help you.
我会帮你。
- He preceded us. - Actually...
- 他走在我们前面 - 事实上...
We must come in billions.
我们必须投入数十亿美元。
Start the car and wait. We will be back quickly.
启动汽车并等待。我们会很快回来。
You must hurry.
你必须快点。
- Woo Jin, there's a bag under the closet. - Okay.
- 宇进，衣柜下面有一个包 - 好的
Wow! gold bar
哇！金条
- Oh my God. Start packing it! - Okay.
- 我的天啊。开始打包吧！ -好的。
Dollars?
美元？
Do not sit still. Pack it.
不要坐着不动。打包吧。
Good
好的
the curse. Someone was severely beaten.
诅咒。有人被严重殴打。
Are you well
你好吗
Follow me.
跟我来。
Slow down.
减速。
Why is there so much money?
为什么有这么多钱？
faster
快点
They are very heavy.
它们很重。
Good
好的
Call Gun Woo.
给金宇打电话。
Yes, Woo Jin.
是的，吴镇。
Don't stop following me no matter what happens.
无论发生什么，都不要停止关注我。
Good
好的
Damn
该死
the curse
诅咒
Can you go faster, Gun-woo?
建宇，你能走快点吗？
I think the car is currently overloaded.
我认为这辆车目前超载了。
When I give you my signal, you go ahead of me.
当我向你发出信号时，你走在我前面。
Good. I'll try
好的。我会尽力
Get ahead of me now!
现在就走在我前面吧！
Damn
该死
Screw it.
算了。
Ride fast.
骑得快。
They are coming. Hurry more!
他们来了。快点再多一点！
There's a disturbance in the car!
车里有骚乱！
Damn
该死
the curse
诅咒
Screw it. Hang on.
算了。不挂断。
Damn
该死
"Woo Jin!" Are you well
“宇进！” 你好吗
Let's go!
我们走吧！
Push!
推！
more
更多的
"Woo Jin!"
“宇进！”
Push it to the right!
把它推到右边！
Push! more
推！更多的
Speed ​​up!
加快速度！
- Shit. - She stopped.
- 妈的 - 她停了下来
the curse
诅咒
The car broke down. Get down. We have to get the two bags.
汽车出故障了。下来。 我们得拿两个袋子。
Run!
跑步！
Run. quickly
跑步。迅速地
Hey!
嘿！
Run faster!
跑得更快！
Translation of "Walid Muharram"
“瓦利德穆哈拉姆”的翻译